Gain control of your digital real-estate.

Privacy policy
==============

Privacy policy
==============

We respect your privacy. This Policy explains what information we collect about you when you are visiting our Website and using related services. While you browse this website, except for an area that we designate to publishers only, we do not collect your personal information.

### **What Personal Identifiable Information Do We Collect?**

We do not collect and store any personal identifiable information. If you use our reporting interface as a registered publisher, we may store details that you provided to us, for identifying purposes only, as provided in the Publisher Agreement.

### **What Non-Personal Information Do We Collect?**

We may collect and retain certain non-personally identifiable information, such as your browsing details and approximate geo-location for statistics and aggregation purposes that will allow us to develop and improve our website and related services.

### **How do we collect information?**

When you visiting our Website, we may collect and retain the stated information by storing a cookie and pixel tag on your computer. A cookie is a small piece of data sent from a website and stored in a user’s web browser while a user is browsing a website. This cookie shall be stored until you delete it from your computer. At all times, you may choose not to accept cookies from us or delete existing cookies, by accessing your browser preferences.

### **How do we process the Information?**

We process non-personal information and create statistical and aggregated information in order to allow better service and monitor use of the Website (by using third party services, such as Google Analytics).

### **Who has access to the information?**

Apart from our employees and contractors, who are under strict confidentiality and data-protection obligations, third party services (such as Google Analytics) may have access to your non-personal identifiable information.

### **Can you review or remove the Information?**

You can always review or remove your information by contacting us through email at:info@gobrowsi.com

### **What to do if you feel your privacy was invaded?**

If you feel that your privacy was invaded or violated, please contact us directly at privacy@gobrowsi.com and we will inspect such complaints within reasonable time and send you and answer promptly.

© 2024 Browsi, All Rights Reserved.

We use cookies on our website to give you the most relevant experience by remembering your preferences and repeat visits. By clicking “Accept All”, you consent to the use of ALL the cookies. However, you may visit "Cookie Settings" to provide a controlled consent.

Cookie SettingsAccept All

Manage consent

Close

#### Privacy Overview

This website uses cookies to improve your experience while you navigate through the website. Out of these, the cookies that are categorized as necessary are stored on your browser as they are essential for the working of basic functionalities of the website. We also use third-party cookies that help us analyze and understand how you use this website. These cookies will be stored in your browser only with your consent. You also have the option to opt-out of these cookies. But opting out of some of these cookies may affect your browsing experience.

Necessary

 Necessary

Always Enabled

Necessary cookies are absolutely essential for the website to function properly. These cookies ensure basic functionalities and security features of the website, anonymously.

| Cookie | Duration | Description |
| --- | --- | --- |
| cookielawinfo-checkbox-analytics | 11 months | This cookie is set by GDPR Cookie Consent plugin. The cookie is used to store the user consent for the cookies in the category "Analytics". |
| cookielawinfo-checkbox-functional | 11 months | The cookie is set by GDPR cookie consent to record the user consent for the cookies in the category "Functional". |
| cookielawinfo-checkbox-necessary | 11 months | This cookie is set by GDPR Cookie Consent plugin. The cookies is used to store the user consent for the cookies in the category "Necessary". |
| cookielawinfo-checkbox-others | 11 months | This cookie is set by GDPR Cookie Consent plugin. The cookie is used to store the user consent for the cookies in the category "Other. |
| cookielawinfo-checkbox-performance | 11 months | This cookie is set by GDPR Cookie Consent plugin. The cookie is used to store the user consent for the cookies in the category "Performance". |
| viewed\_cookie\_policy | 11 months | The cookie is set by the GDPR Cookie Consent plugin and is used to store whether or not user has consented to the use of cookies. It does not store any personal data. |

Functional

 Functional

Functional cookies help to perform certain functionalities like sharing the content of the website on social media platforms, collect feedbacks, and other third-party features.

Performance

 Performance

Performance cookies are used to understand and analyze the key performance indexes of the website which helps in delivering a better user experience for the visitors.

Analytics

 Analytics

Analytical cookies are used to understand how visitors interact with the website. These cookies help provide information on metrics the number of visitors, bounce rate, traffic source, etc.

Advertisement

 Advertisement

Advertisement cookies are used to provide visitors with relevant ads and marketing campaigns. These cookies track visitors across websites and collect information to provide customized ads.

Others

 Others

Other uncategorized cookies are those that are being analyzed and have not been classified into a category as yet.

SAVE & ACCEPT
